CURRICULUM VITAE of NGUYEN THANH TUNG

PERSONAL INFORMATION

English name: Nguyen Thanh Tung Local name: Nguyen Thanh Tung Birthday: 11 January 1991

Address: 15/615, Nguyen Van Cu, Long Bien, Hanoi

Mobile: (+84) 167-876-4642

Email: <u>tung.tung11191@gmail.com</u>

GENERAL PROFILE

I had a strong background with 5+ years of software development. I am advanced and highly familiar with a wide variety of programming language and database management system.

I has been appointed as a leader of Sensor team. With strong leader, I have to motivate teams to deliver effective solutions and the highest levels of performance. I am able to demonstrate the motivation and commitment required to achieve objectives and meet tight deadlines.

On the other hand, I possess excellent interpersonal skills and can communicate concisely at all levels.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Strong technical background
- Application Development
- Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)
- Directing complex design, build and run programmes
- Project management
- Business analysis and process redesign
- Excellent communicator at all levels in English

EDUCATION

2009 - 2013: Department: Faculty of Information Technology (FIT) – Hanoi University

Major: Computer Science.

Grade: Good. Bachelor degree

2015 - present: VNU University of Engineering and Technology

Major: Information System

Master degree Status: Progressing

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

3/2017 – present: Senior staff at Tan Hoang Minh Group

- Develop Recruitment module:
 - Manage Job position, applicant.
 - Manage applicant CV.
 - Manage applicant Interview process
 - o Create recruitment website
 - Analyze and implement a recruitment process from applicant to become employee
 - ⇒ Programming language: Python
 - ⇒ Framework: Odoo ERP
- Develop Online Testing module:



- Manage Question Bank
- Manage User quiz, department quiz,
- Support Multiple choice question. Single choice question, Fill the gap Question, Long Answer question.
- Manage User result and deliver criteria for pass/fail result.
- ⇒ Programming language: Python
- ⇒ Framework: Odoo ERP
- Develop Asset management module
 - Manage company equipment information like; equipment type (phone, laptop, desktop,...), owner, warranty history,...
 - Manage inventory from asset manager
 - Manage asset borrowing requests from user
 - ⇒ Programming language: Python
 - ⇒ Framework: Odoo ERP
- Integrate Google Drive
 - Use Google drive as a Storage to store attachment
 - o All function such as create, edit, delete, ... like Google Drive
 - Create a new widget to be able to drag and drop files
 - ⇒ Programming language: Pvthon
 - ⇒ Framework: Odoo ERP
- Customize Project module:
 - Change project portal website which is easy for customer to follow project task base on timeline theme.
- Attend SAP ERP training course:
 - Using Abap programming language to generate some report to support a lot of department.
- Develop loyalty card system and coupon which support CRM and sale system in both Point of sale module, Sale module and ecommerce website (https://fory.vn).
 - ⇒ Programming language: Python
 - ⇒ Framework: Odoo ERP

2013 -3/2017:

Engineer at Samsung Electronics Vietnam Mobile R&D Center (SVMC), PVI Tower, No 1, Pham Van Bach, Yen Hoa, CauGiay, Ha Noi, Viet Nam.

- Tool Development team: System Analysis and Design, Big Data solution and code implementation in developing Automation Graphical Verification Tools (GRAVETO tool).
- Performance Analysis team:
 - o analyze performance issues on mobile apps (memory leak, sluggish, current consumption),
 - as a developer in developing code analyzing tools (Java, HTML, and JavaScript).
- · Sensor team:
 - as a white box tester in Sensor SDK testing for Motion, Gesture and Fingerprint modules (Java), UV sensor, Camera, Dual Screen,...
 - as a developer in developing document and project management system.
 - as a developer in developing UV channel application (Android app and Gear app)- This application using UV sensor SDK to detect and measure the intensity of incident ultraviolet(UV).
 - o as a developer in developing Hologram Application.
 - As a developer in developing Hotel Management System (using cross Platform like ionic, angular, ...)
- Web App team: as a white box tester in Tizen SDK testing (HTML & JavaScript, Java).

2012 - 2013:

DKA company - specializes in providing solutions for enterprise management.

- CRM project: as a developer in customer relationship management system.
- HR project: as a developer in human resource management system.
- Library project: as a developer in school libary management system.

TECHNOLOGY SUMARY

- Languages: C++, C#, Java, PHP, Javascript, Html, Python
- Systems: Unix, Windows, .Net Framework
- Databases: Oracle, SQL server, Access, Mysql, Postgresql, Sqlite, MongoDB
- Development Tools: Eclipse, Android Studio, Netbeen, Dreamweaver, Visual Express

CERTIFICATE

- TOEIC 790, issued from 12/05/2015 12/05/2017
- SW Advance Level Certificate, Samsung Global Developer Contest

OTHER ACTIVITY AND INTEREST

- I am sporty person in the sense that I have always been actives in some type of sport all
 my life.
 - o I join my company football team from the beginning.
 - o member of badminton, taekwondo club.
- · Reading book, especially Nguyen Nhat Anh 's books